http://www.minimidimaxi.com/Canadian_fashion/B2B_Portal/legal/terms_of_service.html

Terms of Service
"minimidimaxi" -- The Canadian Fashion Stage ©
Minimidimaxi Ltd. - Canadian Fashion Stage ("CFS") maintains this website (our "Site") as a service to the Internet community, as well as business community. By using website owned and operated by Minimidimaxi Ltd.
YOUR USE OF THE SITE AS DESCRIBED ABOVE CONSTITUTES YOUR REPRESENTATION TO "CFS" THAT YOU ARE OVER 18 YEARS OF AGE, THAT YOU MAY LEGALLY ENTER INTO THIS AGREEMENT, AND THAT YOU AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THE AGREEMENT.
IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS AGREEMENT, YOU SHOULD NOT USE THE SITE. WE MAY MODIFY THIS AGREEMENT (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE "CFS" PRIVACY POLICY) FROM TIME TO TIME, AND POST THOSE MODIFICATIONS HERE. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SITE AFTER ANY SUCH MODIFICATION CONSTITUTES YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE MODIFIED AGREEMENT."CFS" MAY TERMINATE THIS AGREEMENT, INCLUDING ALL YOUR RIGHTS HEREUNDER, AT ANY TIME UPON NOTICE, WITH OR WITHOUT CAUSE.
IF YOU WISH TO BE NOTIFIED OF ANY MODIFICATIONS TO THIS AGREEMENT
BY EMAIL, PLEASE CLICK HERE, PROVIDE
A VALID EMAIL ADDRESS AND TYPE "NOTIFY" IN THE EMAIL CONTENT. YOU
UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT YOU SHALL BE BOUND BY ALL SUCH MODIFICATIONS,
IF ANY, REGARDLESS OF WHETHER YOU PROVIDE SUCH EMAIL ADDRESS.
1. Membership
This service is provided exclusively for for-profit and not-for-profit
businesses related to the Canadian fashion industry. As the author
of membership page hosted by "CFS",
you take full responsibility for its contents. The membership pages
hosted by "CFS"
may not contain
anything illegal, pornographic, degrading or abusive to another
person, including gambling, as well as pages that promote hate-group
propaganda, nor may they provide material that is grossly offensive
to the Web community, including blatant expressions of bigotry,
racism, hatred, or profanity, or for promoting or providing instructional
information about illegal activities, or promoting physical harm
or injury against any group or individual. Neither copyrighted material
not belonging to you nor copies of any other page and/or images
may be posted on the membership pages hosted by "CFS"
without prior consent from the copyright holder and/or originator
of the other page and/or images. "CFS"
has the right
to remove any page it determines, in its sole judgment, to be in
violation of these conditions.
2. Registration and Personal Information
The collection or use of personal information by "CFS"
shall be governed by the "CFS"
Privacy Policy, as modified from time to time by "CFS"
; the
terms of such Privacy Policy are hereby incorporated into this Agreement
by reference. You understand and agree that the collection or use
of your personal information by third parties shall be governed
by any agreement or privacy policy in effect between you and such
third parties, if any, and "CFS"
shall
have no liability whatsoever for any such collection or use.
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving
communications from us and our partners at the point on our site
where we request information about the visitor. This site gives
users the following options for removing their information from
our database, to not receive future communications, or to no longer
receive our service.
1. You can contact us at the following URL:
http://www.minimidimaxi.com/Canadian_fashion/B2B_Portal/contact.shtml
2. You can subscribe/unsubscribe to our Fashion Newsletter at the following URL:
http://www.minimidimaxi.com/Canadian_fashion/subscribe.html
3. E-mail Policy - UCE/UBE/spam
You may not send unsolicited email to anyone at anytime under any circumstances.
As all our emails go through automated multi stage filtering system and all unwonted emails (included Spam/UCE) are being automatically reported / redirected in live time to several international anti spam organizations to make sure they are blocked permanently ASAP world wide (at IP source and at the domain - included ISP and/or host providers).
Minimidimaxi Ltd. reserves the rights to include any record history regarding to a such report and/or any related domains/IP in a such report.
Minimidimaxi Ltd. may chose to make it public by any means necessary included but not restricted to any correspondence related to it.
Minimidimaxi Ltd. may choose to block IP netblocks from sending emails through our network and/or access it (included any our IP/domain and/or our clients). Blocked IP may include Sender, Spamvertized URL/domain and/or any one related to a such accident (included ISP and/or host providers).
SPAM CLEANUP FEE of $1000 for server time, technician time and lost productivity will be applied to Companies, Individuals find being involved in accident and $500 SPAM FEE for each and every complaint/email which we received from other mail servers, dialup accounts or our network.
Any direct promotional advertising campaign by email regarding endorsement of any product, entertainment or services is going to be treated as a spam.
Only accounts which subscribed to such services will be excluded from charges.
Please confirm with us if you are not sure if the mailing list which you are about to use is legitimate and all our emails and/or our clients where only directly opt-in to you (not just taken from a business card or from "friends") or third party mailing list.
This Policy applys also to all websites hosted on all our servers.
IN NO EVENT SHALL "CFS",
ITS PARENT, SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATED COMPANIES, AGENTS, SHAREHOLDERS,
EMPLOYEES OR OFFICERS HAVE ANY LIABILITY HEREUNDER TO YOU OR ANY
THIRD PARTY FOR ANY INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL
DAMAGES (INCLUDING DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS, LOSS OF PROFITS,
LITIGATION, OR THE LIKE), WHETHER BASED ON BREACH OF CONTRACT, BREACH
OF WARRANTY, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), PRODUCT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE,
EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. IN NO EVENT
SHALL THE AGGREGATE LIABILITY OF "CFS",
ITS PARENT, SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATED COMPANIES, AGENTS, SHAREHOLDERS,
EMPLOYEES AND OFFICERS EXCEED ONE TEN DOLLARS ($10), REGARDLESS
OF THE CAUSE OF ACTION, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, OR OTHERWISE.
THE NEGATION OF DAMAGES SET FORTH ABOVE ARE FUNDAMENTAL ELEMENTS
OF THE BASIS OF THE BARGAIN BETWEEN "CFS"
AND YOU. THIS SITE AND THE MATERIALS WOULD NOT BE PROVIDED WITHOUT
SUCH LIMITATIONS.
Contacting Abuse Crew: abuse [at] minimidimaxi.net
If you have any questions about this AGREEMENT, you can contact us.
COPYRIGHT NOTICE. Copyright © 2000-2007 minimidimaxi ltd.
All rights reserved.
Minimidimaxi - Canadian Fashion Stage - B2B Portal for the Canadian Fashion
